Guide to the Rosetta Reitz Papers, 1929-2008
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audio and Moving Image Series, 1929-2002, (15 boxes)
  - 16mm Film, 1929-1977 and undated
    - F117: Sally Gooding Mills Blue Rhythm Band, unlabelled and Love is the Thing (12 minutes) (Box 30)
    - F118: Ida Cox, Kentucky Blues (Box 30)
    - F119: Am I Blue? poor copy (Box 30)
    - F120: Bessie Smith, St. Louis Blues (16 minutes) (Box 31)
    - F121: Alberta Hunter (16 ½ minutes) (Box 31)
    - F122: Marian McPartland, Now’s the Time 1977 (10 minutes) (Box 31)
    - F123: Mills Blue Rhythm Band, Cops Dance; Mae Barnes Dr. Jazz; Stormy Weather from A Bundle of Blues (Box 31)
    - F124: Jazz Women on Film (Ivie Anderson, All God’s Children Got Rhythm; Dorothy Dandridge, Harlem Sandman; Helen Humes, I Cried for You; Sister Rosetta Tharpe, Lonesome Road; Maxine Sullivan, Some of These Days; Ethel Waters, Darkies Never Cry; International Sweethearts of Rhythm) (Box 31)
    - F125: Mamie Smith, Jailhouse Blues 1929; Fats Waller and Ada Brown, That Ain’t Right; Sarah Vaughan, These Things I Offer You; Dorothy Donegan, 1945 (Box 31)
    - F126: Billie Holiday with Louis Armstrong, Do You Know What it Means to Miss New Orleans and Blues are Brewin 1947 (Box 31)
    - F127: Rita Rio and Her Mistresses of Rhythm and Ada Leonard’s All-American Girl Orchestra (Box 32)
    - F128: Jazz Women on Film (Billie Holiday, Symphony in Black 1934; Adelaide Hall, Creole Love Call 1932; Valaida Snow, If You Only Knew 1946; Dolly Jones, Swing 1937; Valaida Snow, Patience and Fortitude; Nellie Lutcher, He’s a Real Gone Guy 1955) (Box 32)
    - F129: Velma Middleton; and Ina Ray Hutton and Her Melodears (Box 32)
    - F133: Nina Mae McKinney, Everything I’ve Got Belongs To You; Ethel Waters, Am I Blue and Underneath the Harlem Moon; Ida Cox, Woman’s No Fool; Billie Holiday, God Bless the Child and Now Baby or Never (Box 32)
    - F130: Bessie Smith, St. Louis Blues (Box 33)
    - F131: Chicago and All That Jazz (Box 33)
    - F132: Shouters and Wailers (Ethel Waters, Am I Blue and Birmingham Bertha 1929; Nina Mae McKinney, Sewannee Shuffle; Dinah Washington, What a Difference a Day Makes; Lena Horne, Boogie Woogie Dream 1941; Peggy Lee, Why Don’t You Do Right? 1943; Ella Fitzgerald, Satin Doll; Billie Holiday, Fine and Mellow 1957) (Box 34)
- Reference Materials Series 1946-2005, (23 boxes)
  Contains the resources that Reitz compiled and referenced as a part of her ongoing research and writing. While most of the material relates to her interests in female jazz and blues musicians, some encompasses her interests in feminism more broadly and a lesser portion relates to her interests in food.
  - Music Research Files
    Reference materials--primarily newspaper clippings--compiled by Reitz and arranged alphabetically by musician's last name or subject heading.
    - Akiyoshi, Toshiko (Box 35)
    - Alive! (Box 35)
    - Allen, Geri (Box 35)
    - Anderson, Ernestine (Box 35)
    - Anderson, Ivy (Box 35)
    - Anderson, Marian (Box 35)
    - Armatrading, Joan (Box 35)
    - Armstrong, Lil Hardin (Box 35)
    - Armstrong, Louis (Box 35)
    - Austin, Lovie (Box 35)
    - Badu, Erykah (Box 35)
    - Bailey, Mildred (Box 35)
    - Baker, Josephine (Box 35)
    - Baker, La Vern (Box 35)
    - Barker, Louise Blue Lou (Box 35)
    - Barrett, Sweet Emma (Box 35)
    - Basie, Count (Box 35)
    - Bearden, Romare (Box 35)
    - Benjamin, Sathima Bea (Box 35)
    - Black and Blue Broadway Review (Box 35)
    - Black Broadway Musical (Box 35)
    - Blackman, Cindy (Box 35)
    - Blake, Eubie (Box 35)
    - Bloom, Jane Ira (Box 35)
    - Blues In The Night Musical (Box 35)
    - Bofill, Angela (Box 35)
    - Boswell Sisters (Box 35)
    - Bougainvillea (Box 35)
    - Bown, Patti (Box 35)
    - Brooks, Hadda (Box 35)
    - Brown, Cleo (Box 35)
    - Brown, Ruth (Box 35)
    - Bryant, Beulah (Box 35)
    - Bryant, Clora (Box 35)
    - Buggs, Marie (Box 35)
    - Butterbeans and Susie (Susie Edwards) (Box 35)
    - Calloway, Blanche (Box 35)
    - Carlisle, Una Mae (Box 35)
    - Carmichael, Judy (Box 35)
    - Carpenter, Thelma (Box 35)
    - Carter, Betty (Box 35)
    - Carter, Nell (Box 35)
    - Cheatham, Jeannie (Box 35)
    - Clooney Rosemary (Box 35)
    - Coquettes, the (Box 35)
    - Cron, Roz (Box 35)
    - Davis, Martha (Box 35)
    - Dillard, Kathy (Box 35)
    - Dixie Belles, the (Box 35)
    - Dixon, Lucille (Box 35)
    - Donegan, Dorothy (Box 35)
    - Donnas, the (Box 35)
    - Dranes, Arizona (Box 35)
    - Dufty, Bill (Box 35)
    - Duncan, Amy (Box 35)
    - Etting, Ruth (Box 35)
    - Europe, James Reese (Box 35)
    - Fairfax, Joan (orchestra) (Box 35)
    - Fields, Dorothy (Box 35)
    - Fitzgerald, Ella (Box 36)
    - Flanagan, Tommy (Box 36)
    - Franklin, Aretha (Box 36)
    - Franks, Rebecca (Box 36)
    - Gibson, Althea (Box 36)
    - Gilbert, Peggy (Dixie Bells) (Box 36)
    - Gossett, Hattie (Box 36)
    - Great Migration, The (Box 36)
    - Hall, Adelaide (Box 36)
    - Handy, W.C. (Box 36)
    - Harlem Renaissance (Box 36)
    - Henderson, Rosa (Box 36)
    - Holiday, Billie (Box 36)
    - Holley, Major Mule (Box 36)
    - Holman, Libby (Box 36)
    - Hopkins, Linda (Box 36)
    - Horn, Shirley (Box 36)
    - Horne, Lena (Box 36)
    - Humes, Helen (Box 36)
    - Hunter, Alberta (Box 36)
    - Hutton, Ina Ray (and her Melodears) (Box 36)
    - International Sweethearts of Rhythm (Box 36)
    - Jacquet, Illinois (Box 36)
    - James, Etta (Box 36)
    - Johnson, J.C. (Box 36)
    - Johnson, Lil (Box 36)
    - Jones, Etta (Box 36)
    - Jones, Rickie Lee (Box 36)
    - Jordan, Sheila (Box 36)
    - Kane, Helen (Box 36)
    - Kirk, Dorthaan (Box 36)
    - Koenigswarter, Baroness Pannonica de (Box 36)
    - Lawrence, Carol (Box 36)
    - Lee, Julia (Box 36)
    - Lee, Peggy (Box 36)
    - Lewis, Helen (Box 36)
    - Lilith Fair (Box 36)
    - Lincoln, Abbey (Box 36)
    - Liston, Melba (Box 36)
    - Lundy, Carmen (Box 36)
    - Lutcher, Nellie (Box 36)
    - Mabley, Jackie Moms (Box 36)
    - Maiden Voyage (Box 36)
    - Maria, Tania (Box 36)
    - Massé, Laurel (Box 36)
    - McKinney, Nina Mae (Box 36)
    - McPartland, Marian (Box 36)
    - McRae, Carmen (Box 37)
    - McShann, Jay (Box 37)
    - Memphis Minnie (Lizzie Douglas) (Box 37)
    - Mercer, Mabel (Box 37)
    - Merrill, Helen (Box 37)
    - Midler, Bette (Box 37)
    - Monk, Thelonious (Box 37)
    - Muldaur, Maria (Box 37)
    - Murphy, Rose (Box 37)
    - Narita, Cobi (Universal Jazz Coalition) (Box 37)
    - O'Day, Anita (Box 37)
    - Odetta (Box 37)
    - Osborne, Mary (Box 37)
    - Parker, Gloria (Box 37)
    - Pfister Sisters (Box 37)
    - Phillips, Esther (Box 37)
    - Pierce, Billie (Box 37)
    - Piney Woods School (Box 37)
    - Queen Ida (Box 37)
    - Queen Latifa (Box 37)
    - Ragtime Revival (Box 37)
    - Rainey, Ma (Box 37)
    - Reaves-Phillips, Sandra (Box 37)
    - Redd, Vi (Box 37)
    - Reese, Della (Box 37)
    - Remler, Emily (Box 37)
    - Rhythm Queens (Box 37)
    - Richmond, June (Box 37)
    - Ronstadt, Linda (Box 37)
    - Ross, Annie (Box 37)
    - Saffire (Box 37)
    - Schaap, Phil (Box 37)
    - Scott, Hazel (Box 37)
    - Scott, Shirley (Box 37)
    - Sherman, Daryl (Box 37)
    - Siegel, Janis (Box 37)
    - Simone, Nina (Box 37)
    - Small, Neva (Box 37)
    - Smith, Bessie (Box 37)
    - Smith, Carrie (Box 37)
    - Smith, Ernie (Box 37)
    - Smith, Mamie (Box 37)
    - Snow, Valaida (Box 37)
    - Spivey, Victoria (Box 37)
    - Stone, Evelyn (Box 37)
    - Stone, Jesse (Box 37)
    - Streeter, Sarah (Box 37)
    - Streisand, Barbra (Box 38)
    - String Fever (Box 38)
    - Sudler, Monnette (Box 38)
    - Sullivan, Maxine (Box 38)
    - Sweet Honey in the Rock (Box 38)
    - Taliaferro, Bessie Benjamin (Box 38)
    - Tanguay, Eva (Box 38)
    - Taylor, Koko (Box 38)
    - Tharpe, Sister Rosetta (Box 38)
    - Theodore, Laura (Box 38)
    - Thomas, Irma (Box 38)
    - Thornton, Big Mama (Box 38)
    - Tipton, Billy (Box 38)
    - Tucker, Sophie (Box 38)
    - Vaughan, Sarah (Box 38)
    - Walker, C.J. (Box 38)
    - Wallace, Sippie (Box 38)
    - Washington, Dinah (Box 38)
    - Waters, Ethel (Box 38)
    - Webster, Katie (Box 38)
    - West, Mae (Box 38)
    - White, Georgia (Box 38)
    - Wiley, Lee (Box 38)
    - Williams, Mary Lou (Box 38)
    - Wilson, Cassandra (Box 38)
    - Wilson, Edith (Box 38)
    - Wilson, John S. (Box 38)
    - Wilson, Nancy (Box 38)
    - Women in Jazz (general) (Box 38)
    - Women's Jam Sessions (Box 38)
    - Women's Jazz Festival (Box 38)
    - Women's Philharmonic (Box 38)
    - Wynters, Gail (Box 38)
    - Yancey, Mama (Box 38)
    - Reference Index Cards on Female Musicians (Box 39)
      Handwritten index cards, generally containing an artist's name and one or two sentences of reference information on that artist.
  - Magazines and Journals
    Primarily related to music but some related to food and feminist issues.
    - Acoustic Guitar (January 1996) vol. 37 (Box 40)
    - American Folk Music and Folklore Recordings: a selected list (1985) (Box 40)
    - American Folk Music and Folklore Recordings: a selected list (1987) (Box 40)
    - American Folk Music and Folklore Recordings: a selected list (1988) (Box 40)
    - American Folk Music and Folklore Recordings: a selected list (1989) (Box 40)
    - American Folk Music and Folklore Recordings: a selected list (1991) (Box 40)
    - American Heritage (November 1997) vol. 48 no. 7 (Box 40)
    - American Legacy (Spring 2001) vol. 7 no. 1 (Box 40)
    - And All That Jazz (December 1995) (Box 40)
    - And All That Jazz (May 1996) (Box 40)
    - And All That Jazz (June 1996) (Box 40)
    - ASCAP (Summer 1998) (Box 40)
    - ASCAP Playback (March/April 1996) vol. 3 no. 2 (Box 40)
    - ASCAP Playback (October 1996) vol. 3 no. 4 (Box 40)
    - ASCAP Playback (November/December 1995) vol. 2 no. 6 (Box 40)
    - Augusta Heritage Center (1995) (Box 40)
    - BE (Black Elegance) (June/July 1992) vol. 57 (Box 40)
    - Black American Literature Forum (Winter 1983) vol. 16 no. 4 (Box 40)
    - Il Blues (March 1984) vol. 6 (Box 40)
    - Blues Access (Fall 1990) vol. 1 no. 3 (Box 40)
    - Blues Access (Holiday 1992) vol. 12 (Box 40)
    - Blues Access (Winter 1995) vol. 20 (Box 40)
    - Blues Access (Spring 1995) vol. 21 (Box 40)
    - Blues Access (Summer 1995) vol. 22 (Box 40)
    - Blues Access (Fall 1995) vol. 23 (Box 40)
    - Blues Access (Winter 1996) vol. 24 (Box 40)
    - Blues Access (Winter 1997) vol. 28 (Box 40)
    - The Blues and Rhythm Jubilee (December 1983) vol. 12 no. 13 (Box 40)
    - The Blues and Rhythm Jubilee (June 1984) vol. 14 (Box 40)
    - Blues and Rhythm: the Gospel Truth (April 1985) vol. 8 (Box 40)
    - Blues and Rhythm: the Gospel Truth (September 1985) vol. 12 (Box 40)
    - Blues and Rhythm: the Gospel Truth (May 1986) vol. 19 (Box 40)
    - Blues and Rhythm: the Gospel Truth (June 1986) vol. 20 (Box 40)
    - Blues and Rhythm: the Gospel Truth (July 1996) vol. 21 (Box 40)
    - Blues and Rhythm: the Gospel Truth (September 1986) vol. 23 (Box 40)
    - Blues and Rhythm: the Gospel Truth (October 1986) vol. 23 (Box 40)
    - Blues and Rhythm: the Gospel Truth (November 1986) vol. 24 (Box 40)
    - Blues and Rhythm: the Gospel Truth (December 1986) vol. 25 (Box 40)
    - Blues at the Foundation (Spring/Summer 1996) (Box 40)
    - Blues at the Foundation (Winter 1996) (Box 40)
    - Blues Forum (Quartal 1982) vol. 6 no. 2 (Box 40)
    - Blues Letter (July/Aug. 1990) vol. 11 (Box 40)
    - Blues Letter (September/October 1990) vol. 12 (Box 40)
    - Blues Life (1981) vol. 14 (Box 40)
    - Blues News (January 1996) vol. 9 no. 1 (Box 40)
    - Blues News (March 1995) vol. 8 no. 2 (Box 40)
    - Blues News (May 1995) vol. 8 no. 3 (Box 40)
    - Blues News (July 1995) vol. 8 no. 4 (Box 40)
    - Blues News (November 1994) vol. 7 no. 6 (Box 40)
    - Blues News (November 1995) vol. 8 no. 6 (Box 40)
    - Blues To-Do's (November 1994) vol. 2 no. 11 (Box 41)
    - Blues To-Do's (March 1995) vol. 3 no. 3 (Box 41)
    - Blues To-Do's (April 1995) vol. 3 no. 4 (Box 41)
    - Blues To-Do's (May 1995) vol. 3 no. 5 (Box 41)
    - Blues To-Do's (June 1995) vol. 3 no. 6 (Box 41)
    - Blues To-Do's (October 1995) vol. 3 no. 10 (Box 41)
    - Blues To-Do's (November 1995) vol. 3 no. 11 (Box 41)
    - Blues To-Do's (December 1995) vol. 3 no. 12 (Box 41)
    - Blues To-Do's (February 1996) vol. 4 no. 2 (Box 41)
    - Blues To-Do's (March 1996) vol. 4 no. 3 (Box 41)
    - Blues To-Do's (April 1996) vol. 4 no. 4 (Box 41)
    - Blues To-Do's (May 1996) vol. 4 no. 5 (Box 41)
    - Blues To-Do's (July 1996) vol. 4 no. 7 (Box 41)
    - Blues To-Do's (August 1996) vol. 4 no. 8 (Box 41)
    - Blues To-Do's (September 1996) vol. 4 no. 9 (Box 41)
    - Blues To-Do's (October 1996) vol. 4 no. 10 (Box 41)
    - Blues To-Do's (November 1996) vol. 4 no. 11 (Box 41)
    - Blues To-Do's (December 1996) vol. 4 no. 12 (Box 41)
    - Blues To-Do's (January 1997) vol. 5 no. 1 (Box 41)
    - Blues To-Do's (February 1997) vol. 5 no. 2 (Box 41)
    - Blues To-Do's (March 1997) vol. 5 no. 3 (Box 41)
    - Blues To-Do's (May 1997) vol. 5 no. 5 (Box 41)
    - Blues To-Do's (January 1998) vol. 6 no. 1 (Box 41)
    - Broomstick (May/June 1986) vol. 8 no. 3 (Box 41)
    - Broomstick (May/July 1985) vol. 7 no. 3, 4 (Box 41)
    - Cadence (May 1986) vol. 12 no. 5 (Box 41)
    - Cadence (December 1990) vol. 16 no. 12 (Box 41)
    - Centerpoint (Fall/Spring 1980) vol. 3 no. 3, 4 (Box 41)
    - Coda (August 1973) vol. 11 no. 2 (Box 41)
    - Coda (April 1980) vol. 174 (Box 41)
    - Coda (June 1983) vol. 190 (Box 41)
    - Coda (February/March 1987) vol. 212 (Box 41)
    - Coda (April/May 1987) vol. 213 (Box 41)
    - Coda (June/July 1987) vol. 214 (Box 41)
    - Coda (August/September 1987) vol. 215 (Box 41)
    - Coda (April/May 1988) vol. 219 (Box 41)
    - Coda (October/November 1988) vol. 222 (Box 41)
    - Coda (February 1979) vol. 164, 165 (Box 41)
    - Conditions (1979) vol. 5 (Box 41)
    - CRC Jazz Journal (September-December 1987) vol. 8 no. 4 (Box 41)
    - Daedelus Music (Winter 2002) (Box 41)
    - Daedelus Music (Fall 2003) (Box 41)
    - Daedelus Music (Winter 2003) (Box 41)
    - Daedelus Music (Winter 2004) (Box 41)
    - Daybreak M.O. (Summer 1994) (Box 41)
    - Different Drummer (January 1974) vol. 1 no. 4 (Box 41)
    - The Dippermouth News (Fall 1999) vol. 1 no. 1 (Box 41)
    - Double Time Jazz (Spring 96) (Box 41)
    - Double Time Jazz (Summer 96) (Box 41)
    - Double Time Jazz (n/a) (Box 41)
    - Down Beat (November 1973) vol. 40 no. 19 (Box 41)
    - Down Beat (December 1989) vol. 56 no. 12 (Box 41)
    - Down Beat (February 1990) vol. 57 no. 2 (Box 41)
    - Down Beat (June 1990) vol. 57 no. 6 (Box 41)
    - Down Beat (July 1990) vol. 57 no. 7 (Box 41)
    - Film Hits (February 1996) (Box 41)
    - Film Hits (April 1996) (Box 41)
    - Freedomways (Fall 1985) (Box 41)
    - Frontiers: A Journal of Women Studies (January 1993) vol. 8 no. 2 (Box 41)
    - Fuse (Fall 1985) vol. 9 no. 3 (Box 41)
    - The Green Mountain Jazz Messenger (April/May 1998) vol. 1 no. 5 (Box 41)
    - Harlem Youth Report (June 1964) vol. 5 (Box 41)
    - Helicon Nine (1985) vol. 17, 18 (Box 42)
    - Helicon Nine (1987) vol. 12, 13 (Box 42)
    - Helicon Nine (1988) vol. 19 (Box 42)
    - Helicon Nine (1989) vol. 20 (Box 42)
    - Heresies (1980) vol. 10 (Box 42)
    - Hot Club de France (June 1985) vol. 3 no. 328 (Box 42)
    - Hot Wire (March 1985) vol. 1 no. 2 (Box 42)
    - Hot Wire (September 1989) vol. 5 no. 3 (Box 42)
    - Hot Wire (September 1990) vol. 6 no. 3 (Box 42)
    - Hot Wire (January 1991) vol. 7 no. 1 (Box 42)
    - Hot Wire (May 1991) vol. 7 no. 2 (Box 42)
    - Hot Wire (January 1992) vol. 8 no. 1 (Box 42)
    - Hot Wire (May 1992) vol. 8 no. 2 (Box 42)
    - Hot Wire (September 1992) vol. 8 no. 3 (Box 42)
    - Hot Wire (May 1993) vol. 9 no. 2 (Box 42)
    - Hot Wire (May 1994) vol. 10 no. 2 (Box 42)
    - Inside Arts (September 1991) vol. 3 no. 3 (Box 42)
    - Jan Scobey's Hot Jazz (1995) (Box 42)
    - Jan Scobey's Hot Jazz (1996) (Box 42)
    - Jan Scobey's Hot Jazz (2000) (Box 42)
    - Jazz (July 1996) vol. 1 no. 10 (Box 42)
    - Jazz (August 1996) vol. 1 no. 11 (Box 42)
    - Jazz (September 1996) vol. 1 no. 12 (Box 42)
    - Jazz (October 1996) vol. 2 no. 1 (Box 42)
    - Jazz (March 1999) vol. 4 no. 4 (Box 42)
    - Jazz Beat (August 1989) vol. 1 no. 1 (Box 42)
    - Jazz Forum (May 1988) vol. 114 (Box 42)
    - Jazz Journal (November 1975) vol. 28 no. 11 (Box 42)
    - Jazz Journal (December 1955) vol. 8 no. 12 (Box 42)
    - Jazz Magazine (Spring 1978) vol. 2 no. 3 (Box 42)
    - Jazz Magazine (Fall 1979) vol. 3 no. 4 (Box 42)
    - Jazz Magazine (Fr.) (January 1983) vol. 314 (Box 42)
    - Jazz Magazine (Fr.) (March 1983) vol. 316 (Box 42)
    - Jazz Magazine (Fr.) (November 1983) vol. 323 (Box 42)
    - Jazz News (May/June 1988) vol. 2 no. 2 (Box 43)
    - Jazz News (September/October 1988) vol. 2 no. 4 (Box 43)
    - Jazz Newsletter (December 1994) vol. 6 (Box 43)
    - Jazz Notes (2001) vol. 12 no. 1 (Box 43)
    - Jazz NU (March 1983) vol. 53 (Box 43)
    - The Jazz Report (Fall 1991) vol. 5 no. 1 (Box 43)
    - The Jazz Report (Spring 1991) vol. 5 no. 3 (Box 43)
    - The Jazz Report (Summer 1991) vol. 5 no. 4 (Box 43)
    - The Jazz Report (Fall 1992) vol. 6 no. 1 (Box 43)
    - The Jazz Report (Fall 1993) vol. 7 no. 1 (Box 43)
    - The Jazz Report (Winter 1993) vol. 7 no. 2 (Box 43)
    - The Jazz Report (Spring 1993) vol. 7 no. 3 (Box 43)
    - The Jazz Report (Summer 1993) vol. 7 no. 4 (Box 43)
    - The Jazz Report (Fall 1994) vol. 8 no. 1 (Box 43)
    - The Jazz Report (Summer 1994) vol. 8 no. 4 (Box 43)
    - The Jazz Report (Fall 1995) vol. 9 no. 1 (Box 43)
    - The Jazz Report (Winter 1995) vol. 9 no. 2 (Box 43)
    - The Jazz Report (Spring 1995) vol. 9 no. 3 (Box 43)
    - The Jazz Report (Summer 1995) vol. 9 no. 4 (Box 43)
    - The Jazz Review (January 1959) vol. 2 no. 1 (Box 43)
    - The Jazz Review (September 1991) (Box 43)
    - Jazz Times (February 1994) vol. 24 no. 1 (Box 43)
    - Jazz Times (March 1990) (Box 43)
    - Jefferson (1987) vol. 76 (Box 43)
    - Journal of Jazz Studies (Fall/Winter 1979) vol. 6 no. 1 (Box 43)
    - Juke Blues (October 1985) vol. 2 (Box 43)
    - Juke Blues (Spring 1986) vol. 4 (Box 43)
    - Juke Blues (Autumn 1986) vol. 6 (Box 43)
    - Juke Blues (Winter 1986) vol. 7 (Box 43)
    - Juke Blues (Summer 1987) vol. 9 (Box 43)
    - Juke Blues (Summer 1989) vol. 16 (Box 43)
    - Living Blues (May/June 1977) vol. 32 (Box 43)
    - Living Blues (Summer 1979) vol. 43 (Box 43)
    - Living Blues (Winter 1982) vol. 55 (Box 43)
    - Living Blues (Spring 1983) vol. 56 (Box 43)
    - Living Blues (Autumn 1983) vol. 57 (Box 43)
    - Living Blues (Winter 1983) vol. 58 (Box 43)
    - Living Blues (Spring 1984) vol. 59 (Box 43)
    - Living Blues (March-April 1985) vol. 64 (Box 43)
    - Living Blues (October 1994) vol. 117 (Box 43)
    - Living Blues (Summer/Fall 1984) vol. 60, 61 (Box 43)
    - Masters of the Steel String Guitar (Spring 1990) (Box 43)
    - Menopause (June 1980) vol. 3 (Box 43)
    - Metronome (August 1961) vol. 78 no. 8 (Box 43)
    - The Mississippi Rag (May 1985) (Box 43)
    - The Mississippi Rag (December 1984) (Box 43)
    - The Mississippi Rag (December 1991) (Box 43)
    - The Piano Stylist (April/May 1992) vol. 7 no. 2 (Box 43)
    - Music and Sound Output (December 1988) vol. 9 no. 1 (Box 43)
    - New Directions for Women (March/April 1993) vol. 22 no. 2 (Box 44)
    - New Directions for Women (July/August) vol. 17 no. 4 (Box 44)
    - The New Yorker (January 1995) (Box 44)
    - New Women's Times (May 1980) vol. 6 no. 10 (Box 44)
    - Newport Jazz Festival (1955) cover separated (Box 44)
    - Newport Jazz Festival (1959) (Box 44)
    - Newport Jazz Festival (1980) (Box 44)
    - Newport Jazz Festival (1981) (Box 44)
    - NJSO Journal (1994) vol. 5 no. 1 (Box 44)
    - NJSO Journal (Fall 1990) vol. 1 no. 4 (Box 44)
    - Nonviolent Activist (July/August 2003) vol. 20 no. 4 (Box 44)
    - Note 4 Note (Summer 1997) vol. 26 (Box 44)
    - Now News (Spring/Summer 2002) vol. 29 no. 3 (Box 44)
    - Outlook (spring 1988) vol. 1 no. 1 (Box 44)
    - Past Times (Summer 1990) vol. 1 no. 1 (Box 44)
    - Playback (January/February 2001) vol. 8 no. 1 (Box 44)
    - The Piano Stylist (April/May 1992) vol. 7 no. 2 (Box 44)
    - Popular (June 2001) (Box 44)
    - Popular (July 2001) (Box 44)
    - Popular (August 2001) (Box 44)
    - Popular (September 2001) (Box 44)
    - Radical Teacher (March 1977) vol. 4 (Box 44)
    - Rap Sheet (September 1994) vol. 2 no. 9 (Box 44)
    - Rap Sheet (December 1994) vol. 2 no. 12 (Box 44)
    - Record Research (November/December 1958) vol. 20 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (October 1961) vol. 38 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (October 1965) vol. 71 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (November 1965) vol. 72 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (January 1966) vol. 73 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (March 1966) vol. 74 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (June 1966) vol. 77 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (August 1966) vol. 78 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (October 1966) vol. 79 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (November 1966) vol. 80 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (January 1967) vol. 81 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (March 1967) vol. 82 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (April 1967) vol. 83 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (June 1967) vol. 84 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (August 1967) vol. 85 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (December 1967) vol. 87 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (January 1968) vol. 88 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (March 1968) vol. 89 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (May 1968) vol. 90 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (July 1968) vol. 91 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (September 1968) vol. 92 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (November 1968) vol. 93 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (December 1968) vol. 94 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (April 1969) vol. 96, 97 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (May 1969) vol. 98 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (July 1969) vol. 99 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (August 1969) vol. 100 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (October 1969) vol. 101 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (January 1970) vol. 103 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (March 1970) vol. 104 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (May 1970) vol. 105 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (July 1970) vol. 106 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (October 1970) vol. 107 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (December 1970) vol. 108 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (February 1971) vol. 109 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (May 1971) vol. 110 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (July 1971) (Box 45)
    - Record Research (November/December 1971) vol. 113, 114 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (February 1972) vol. 115 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (May 1972) vol. 116 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (October 1972) vol. 118 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (December/January 1973) vol. 119, 120 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (March 1973) vol. 121 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (June 1973) vol. 122 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (August 1973) vol. 123 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (November 1973) vol. 124 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (February 1974) vol. 125, 126 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (May 1974) vol. 127 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (July 1974) vol. 128 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (October/November 1974) vol. 129, 130 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (January 1975) vol. 131 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (April 1975) vol. 132 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (June 1975) vol. 133 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (August 1975) vol. 134 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (February/March 1976) vol. 137, 138 (Box 45)
    - Record Research (May/June 1976) vol. 139, 140 (Box 45)